duke4.net 2013-04-06

# Duke Nukem 3D, Duke Nukem Forever • Duke4.net: Our Privacy Polcy

We are adopting the following Privacy Policy because we are committed to protecting your privacy. Our Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. The following policies are in effect for the Web pages and discussion forums operated by Duke4.net

 **Information we gather and how we gather it:**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from Duke4.net, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of our network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. We do not share our users' personal information (IE. e-mail and IP address) with third party companies.

 **Cookies**

We may send a "cookie" to your computer depending on the parts of our website you may be accessing. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of Duke4.net you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our website and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online--for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere--that the information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

By using the Duke4.net network, you consent to the collection and use of information by Duke4.net as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Please use our contact page for any inquiries you have regarding our Privacy Policy. You are encouraged to report admin abuse so that we may enhance our services appropriately.
